

Rozhiar Omer

Frontend Web Developer

My Contacts

🛇 🛮 Sulaymanyah, Iraq

rozhiarrashid@gmail.com

+964 771 020 7959

(in) /Rozhiar Rashid/(🗘) Rozhiar-tech

Technical Skills

HTML CSS JavaScript **Tailwind** React Bootstrap **Flutter** Dart NodeJs Next.js **Python**

Projects

Happy- DEMO | CODE

Dec 2022 - Jan 2023 /Full Time

A platform where all middle east can easily find a therapist

JavaScript, React, Firebase, Tailwind

Project Lead handled Frontend and some of the backend as well Used for better performance

Popcorn Store - DEMO | CODE

Nov 2022 - Dec 2022 /Full Time

A place for everyone to pick a movie based on there needs

JavaScript , HTML, Css, Tailwind Handled everything related to the FrontEnd Fething API data organize them

Soft Skill

- Observation
- Decision makina
- Communication
- Multi-tasking
- TeamWork

Languages

- Kurdish Native
- English Full Professional Proficiency. Arabic Limited Working Proficiency

About Me

Hi there! My name is Rozhiar and I am a frontend developer with 6 years of experience building web applications. I am passionate about creating intuitive and visually appealing user interfaces, and I enjoy learning about new technologies and techniques to improve my skills.

Professional Experience

Mobile Application Developer-RozhGroup

Feb 2019 - Jun 20221 /Full Time

- Designing and developing mobile applications for iOS and/or Android platforms. Writing clean, maintainable, and efficient code.
- Collaborating with designers and other team members to develop intuitive and visually appealing
- Ensuring that your code is optimized for performance, security, and accessibility.
- Debugging and fixing issues with mobile applications.
 Ensuring that your code adheres to coding standards and best practices.

Lab assistant- University of Human Development

Sep 2021 -2023

- \bullet Providing technical support to students and faculty using the lab's computer systems and equipment.
- Maintaining and troubleshooting computer hardware and software issues
- Installing and configuring software and operating systems.
- · Assisting with the maintenance and upkeep of the lab's inventory of computers and other
- Assisting with the setup and management of network infrastructure, including switches,
- Providing support for online learning platforms and tools.
- Assisting with the development and maintenance of websites and other online resources.

Frontend Developer- Mazee advertisement

Sep 2022

- Designing and implementing user-facing features for web and mobile applications.
 Building and maintaining efficient, reusable, and reliable front-end code.
- orating with designers and other team members to develop intuitive and visually appealing user interfaces.
- Ensuring that the code you write is optimized for performance, security, and accessibility.
 Debugging and fixing issues with the front end of the web and mobile applications.
- Ensuring that your code adheres to coding standards and best practices
- Staying up to date with new technologies and techniques in front-end developm Participating in code reviews and providing feedback to other team members.
- Mentoring and guiding less experienced team members
- Participating in the design and planning of new projects and features.

Fullstack Developer-department of defense kurdistan regionial government

2023 -current

Education

Frontend Web Development - Re:Coded

Feb 2020 - Jun 2022

Re:Coded Immersive bootcamps are highly competitive, with a 5%

- Completing a 4.5-month immersive design bootcamp, with 300+ hours of curricula and project-based learning
- Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React
- Working with various design teams to create products across industries.

Information Technology -University **Human Development**

Nov 2017 — may 2021

Completing a 4-years immersive design Courses, with 3600-5400 hours of curricula and project-based learning in all IT and CS courses